I'm totally serious! Just hear me out!
Aw, jeez.
For the last time, Mista,
no one gives a shit!
No, listen, this is a
good one, I promise you.
Gentlemen, let me ask you all.
Do you think human flesh would taste
like crap, or would it actually rock?
Could you maybe not
ruin all our appetites?
What the hell goes on in that
messed up head of yours?!
That's it!
Go sit at the dipshit table!
You're gonna stay right where you are
it's the press you must pay the truth?
You'll never come to
experience it's mercy!
I'll kill you. No!
No!
Thank you.
Stay cold.
So, sa, me ni wa me wo.
Laghi ni mono ni wa.
Requiem wo.
Nessuno può sfuggire dal destino scelto.
Roman solo il risultato.
Che voi sarete distrutti.
Oh, we go too late.
The fear of the fear of the world.
The fear of the world is facing.
The fear of the fear is not necessary.
The body will disappear.
Hello, the beginning of the day.
Do the wind.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Damn!
Our boy actually did it!
You and that arrow kicked major ass!
It still beats the hell
out of me what Golden
Wind whatchamacallit's actual powers are.
But the point is, that
bastard's dead now! Hold it.
Don't rejoice yet.
I don't see his body anywhere.
Huh? No! Damn!
How the hell did he manage to get away?
Ah, shit!
Don't just stand there, Giorno!
Help us look!
Which way did he go?
Bungling amateurs!
In the end, you've failed to kill me.
Unsurprising.
Still, something troubles me.
My premonition clearly showed that I
would be the one to prevail, so why?
What twisted powers did Requiem give him?
When I get my hands on you, you'll pay.
But first things first, I must
break free from this damn current.
Excellent!
My luck is turning!
Nice tryachte!
I'll cut you, I swear!
Just try me!
I'll serve you like a deli slice! Ha-ha!
What's wrong, you curious?
I think you think I won't do
it, well think again, bitch!
I'll show your dumb ass!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'll poke you full of holes,
you weird strawberry with legs!
What did you...
Come on!
This can't...
What is this?
I can't...
I can't move! It's my dog!
Why the hell can't I move?
Please help somebody!
This can't be how I died!
I am Diavolo!
A common huddle could
possibly be my undoing!
That doesn't make any sense!
Where am I?
Hold on.
How did I get on this table?
Just a moment ago, I barely
managed to escape the river.
Let's see.
Procedural date is the 25th, time 1120 AM.
File number 68, acting physician, Dr.
Monica Ulltello here.
The deceased looks to be an
adult male, 30 to 40 years old.
Identity is unknown.
Condition of his skin suggests time
of death was 48 to 50 hours ago,
commencing autopsy to
find out cause of death.
Enough of this!
I won't play your sick game!
The body was discovered in
close proximity to the river...
Are you Death Woman?
I demand you explain
yourself now! Hey! Lady!
Not again why can't i
move the hell'd you do
to me what foul curse
i'm talking to you don't
ignore me who do you think
you are put that thing
away damn it why am i
just letting this happen?
The pain!
It's unbearable!
Cause of death is a laceration to
the liver, likely caused by a knife.
The lack of hesitation wounds
means this was not suicide.
I'll open up his abdomen
and check, just to be sure.
His liver's in good health.
The color's excellent.
Thank god was it all just
a horrible nightmare?
No this isn't where i was.
Hold on now what time is it where am i
last i recall i'd been
thrown into the diver
and there was that terrible pain.
I can still feel the cold steel.
It was far too real to
be a damnable dream.
But how am I still alive?
Excuse me.
You okay there, sir?
You really shouldn't sit there.
If you need medical attention,
I can call an ambulance.
Back off, girl.
What is this madness?
None of this makes sense!
How could I meet such an undignified end?
Don't tell me this is...
No!
What have you wrought on
me, Goldenwood Requiem?
We have to find him quick.
I can pick up traces of Azora.
He's still lurking around.
We can't rest until we find him.
Trish, take a breath now.
It's okay. What?
There's nothing to look for anymore.
He won't ever be back.
Even though I couldn't witness
Requiem at work myself,
something deep in my soul
tells me our job is done.
Nothing will ever come within
his putrid reach again.
Not even the truth of his
ultimate fate will grace him.
His own death will remain a
mystery to him for all eternity.
You're sitting funny, mister.
Does your tummy hurt?
It's over.
But we didn't finish him.
His end is without end.
That is Golden Wind Requiem's judgment.
How many deaths must I die?
What'll happen to me next?
How much longer do I
have to wait for the end?
Stay back.
Leave me be.
Don't come closer.
Stay away!
Leave me alone!
So it's over then, finally.
You sure about this?
We really won?
Crap, that's right.
We gotta get back to the Coliseum.
Bucciarati's soul is gonna
need its old body patched up.
And I just know the man's gonna lose his
shit if he wakes up to all of us gone.
Right.
Hey, Giorno! Come on!
Did you hear a word I said?
Let's heal Bucciarati
and head the hell home!
Yeah.
Let's go.
I'm right behind you.
Jonah, you've done enough.
You don't have to worry anymore.
What we've finally accomplished is
nothing short of a full and true victory.
Fate is but a slumbering slave.
One that we have at last
emancipated the day is ours.
Open your minds, fellas!
I'm telling you it's important
to think about what it is you're
eating because that shit is directly
connected to your happiness you?
Look, I know how it
sounds, but I can explain.
So, think of all the
animals that are carnivores.
You know, like the lions,
the cats, and the vultures.
You won't find those meat-eating critters
in a restaurant menu for one
obvious reason. You ready?
Because those nastiest
suckers freakin' reek!
That's why!
They taste like duty!
I mean, you get it, right?
Cat flesh is super nasty.
You with me so far?
News flash, you weirdo!
None of us knows what a cat tastes like,
because we would never
even think to eat one.
All right, just hold on.
Have you ever heard of the sweet fish?
Those guys never touch insects.
They only eat fresh algae.
Some say that's the reason
why their innards taste
a million times better
than all the other fish?
who only snack on disgusting
shit like worms and crickets.
It's their meat-free diets. Hmm.
So it's logical to conclude?
Those sweet animals who don't eat meat.
are actually the ones who produce
the best-tasting meat of all.
Cows, pigs, chickens.
The healthier their diets, the
tastier our dinners, of course!
It's simple math!
Which also means us meat-eating
humans tastes like ass!
I mean, come on!
That's bullet-proof logic! That may be.
It's surprisingly coherent.
Here's the thing, though.
There's a bunch of stories
about how humans taste good,
but we've figured out the truth!
Still, if you're right,
then what does that say about all of the
fruits and vegetables that I usually eat?
Maybe we should throw you
on the grill and find out.
Narancia, God, you are
such an easy target.
Hey, look who it is.
How nice of you to join us.
A man at the airport, a
certain leaky-eyed Luca.
I'm told someone's
discovered his cold body.
We're looking into it.
Direct orders from Cape Polpo.
Who gives a shit about Luca?
You know that asshole had it coming.
That's what he deserves for picking on
the weak and pushing drugs onto kids.
What's there to investigate?
The dumbass probably got
high and hit his head.
Narancia,
your passionate feelings do not excuse
you from choosing your words with care.
Not in our world.
I'll take the job.
Shouldn't be too difficult.
But don't you worry, I won't half-ass it.
Future Kapos like you
shouldn't do grunt work.
No, I'll look into this myself.
That aside, though.
Oh, right.
You have a guest.
Poor guy's been waiting for you all day.
He claims to be a humble flower
shop owner from the piazza.
I've checked the man's story out.
He's an ordinary, hard-working man who lost
his only daughter about six months ago.
Mr.
Bucciarati, as you can plainly see,
my legs aren't what they once were.
But in spite of that,
I've traveled all the way here on my
own today, hoping that I might meet you.
So please forgive me if I
appear shaky at the knees.
My good man, do you pay all your taxes?
I... pardon?
It's a very simple question.
Do you pay what you owe your country?
Every lira of it on time?
Of course.
Fully and never late.
In that case, I would strongly advise you
to take your business elsewhere, good sir.
This is no place for
someone such as yourself.
A normal and honest taxpaying citizen,
one might say, should perhaps avail
himself of his local police station.
For as soon as I hear the
first word of your request,
you will gain a new debt greater than anyone
you've known to me and my dear Family.
That's fine.
Just like every other father, I work hard.
I toil long hours to afford food?
and I try my best, as any father would do!
to raise his children
with love and honesty.
She was my only girl.
It was this past September
that she turned 17.
Please, forgive me for asking,
but I would much prefer it if we could
continue our conversation in private.
While I am sympathetic to your plight,
the men in this room place their absolute
trust in me, and I place mine in them.
So unfortunately, I can't just ask them to
simply interrupt their meal for our sake.
That would be plain rude.
It all happened suddenly a few months ago.
I learned from my wife that our daughter
had gone and found herself a boyfriend.
She told me the young man was a
sculptor just beginning on his way,
but that didn't matter to me.
I didn't even mind that he
was a bit older than her.
Yet never, not once, did he
come to meet me and my wife.
That never sat quite right with me.
Then, all of a sudden,
my precious flower fell from the
roof of that man's apartment.
clutching to her chest some strange rock.
I'm sorry.
I've lost my composure.
Why does the pain still feel
so fresh after all this time?
My daughter was my hope.
She was young and beautiful.
She lit up my world with
her astounding radiance.
I beg you to do everything that you can.
To see that my girl is avenged,
please make that rotten
scoundrel suffer for what he did.
Stop for a moment, you
think she was killed?
Am I hearing you correctly?
And you believe this
boyfriend was the killer?
That he was the one who
pushed her off of the roof?
I must say I find this quite strange.
News of murder in this
town always reaches me.
The police refused to
start an investigation.
They wrote it off as suicide and
swept the case aside like my lawyer.
But as Sir Family, we can
swear to you one thing.
Our beautiful girl would
never have taken her own life.
Both my wife and I know this
to be true in our hearts.
You're my last hope.
There's nobody else left I
can turn to at this point.
I ask you to make that bastard
feel just a fraction of my pain.
Let him have a small taste of what I will
endure for the remainder
of my wretched life.
I'm sorry this world has been
cruel to you, but I can't help.
I'm afraid my condolences
are all I can offer.
Don't mistake us for a band of lowly
ruffians who would kill anyone for money!
But I've seen the things you've
done for the people in town!
All I'm really asking for is
justice for my departed daughter?
You say you want justice?
Signore, not long ago you wished
to speak together in private?
And I've figured out why!
It seems you are perfectly aware
of how dangerous your inquiry is.
Still, I'll admit your devotion to
your Family struck a chord with me.
It's one of my soft spots.
In addition to all that,
I also think it's rather suspicious that
no one else has been moved by your story.
This might just be worth
looking into after all!
I suppose at least, we'll see what
this mysterious sculptor has to say.
I will ask for your payment only
after he has been found guilty.
Do you accept?
God bless your soul, signore.
Mister, I would like to
take you on this assignment.
Sounds good.
What the hell?
Did I lay this thing?
Mista, be sure to put that
back where you found it.
Did I just…
did I knock it over?
Do you know where this
stone was perched earlier?
Because I swear it's almost
like it popped out of the air.
Just watch yourself
when you're standing up.
I prefer my things not
in pieces on the ground.
Mista, Bucciarati says he'll
give you a ride part of the way.
Right.
Take this.
I've written down the sculptor's home
address and here's a picture of our man!
Have a little chat with him.
See what you can find out.
You're free to employ physical coercion
if you need to get a clear confession.
You have your recorder. Yeah.
But just so I know, how far is too far?
Like if it turns out he did
push that poor girl off a roof,
how many bullets am I supposed to use?
Remember we're not assassins.
Let's just put him in a wheelchair
for the rest of the decade.
The police can take it from there.
That should be more than enough
to cool the old man's rage!
Hey.
Where you off to?
Will you stop messing around?
We'll leave you.
Mista, what's the damn
holdup? Need a shit?
Just wait a sec.
I'm doing something important, okay?
You look troubled. What's wrong?
Well,
there's something about
that old man's story
that's rubbing me wrong all
sorts of ways right now.
Like when his daughter fell.
If I'm remembering right,
he mentioned something about her
clutching a weird stone of some sort.
Did he say exactly what
kind of stone it was?
No.
Wait, he said nothing about its shape?
Or even how big it was?
I mean, the freaking dude is
a sculptor, for God's sake.
All he said was it looked strange.
Not much else.
Ah, son of a bitch!
I could name a ton of different
things that look strange.
Unfortunately, it was the
only adjective he gave us.
What's on your mind?
This is sudden.
Wait, it's the stone!
Hey, pull over for a
sec, Fugo! Stop the car!
For what?
Slam the brakes, dammit!
Hey, man, I told you to go before we left.
Uh, yeah. Never mind.
Thought I saw something.
My bad.
Just forget I said anything.
Are you okay, Mista?
I mean, how much wine
did you have to drink?
Hey, why is that always
the first place you go?
I'm not drunk, okay?
Maybe a little loopy.
Think before you speak, man.
Words can hurt, you know?
Wait, isn't that it over there?
All right, let me out.
Jeez, what a drama queen.
I feel bad for him.
Not sure he really wants a friend right
now, but maybe I should just go with him.
It's fine.
I can watch Mista's back.
Better to err on the side of caution.
Those rumors of stand users convening
on our city has me on guard.
Go look into Leaky Eye Leaky.
You got it, Chief.
So, the guy lives on the seventh floor.
And right above it is the roof.
Nice place, Skolipi.
And there's the courtyard.
That's the spot where the old man
said his daughter hit the ground.
That's a stand!
So I wasn't seeing stuff.
This just got a whole
lot more interesting.
Watch out, Rock!
I'm gonna figure out your damn deal!
Butrati...
Thank you.